thebabywearer.com 2013-07-27

# Privacy Policy

This privacy statement applies to the website of:   
TheBabyWearer.com   

We respect your privacy. This is why we have taken the time to disclose our information collection practices and our privacy policy. Please take the time to review this document. 

Collecting information enables us to provide you with news about the site via email and permit registration and login procedures.

**We collect information for the following purpose(s):**  
• Completing and supporting registration and site subscriptions.  
• Website and system administration (only registered users have unlimited access)   
• Maintenance of the Vendor and Products Reviews section   
• Contacting our visitors for administration of the site  
• Other periodic email notifications

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on TheBabywearer.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. This is more information about Google ad privacy available [here](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

No personal information is collected via sponsored ads. However, TheBabywearer.com does not assume responsibility for any content on sites external to our own.  

**Who has access to the information we collect?**  
• Ourselves   
• Registered site users via the forum profiles (except others' email addresses and passwords)

Of the information we do collect, we allow our registered users access to all collected information about themselves. 

If you believe that TheBabyWearer has collected incorrect information or if you would like to dispute any information, please contact us using the email address at the top of this page.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We use Paypal to handle all of our credit card and Paypal payment processing. [Click here](https://cms.paypal.com/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US) to review Paypal’s privacy policy. Because this service is used for subscription payment processing, we never store payment information on our servers. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline or through other sources. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 1/4/2012 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   

© TheBabyWearer.com, 2012. All rights reserved.
